Hello, dear students.
My name is Yulia Romanenko
and I will be your
instructor for this
module titled
Personal Effectiveness.
Have you ever thought
about what personal
effectiveness means to you?
How to manage your time?
How to find a balance between
the different areas of your life?
While being a student,
it seems that time
and energy are unlimited.
Nonetheless, with every passing
year the world around you will
make even greater demands on you.
You will become an employee
of a company or run your own business.
Perhaps, you will start
a family and become
a parent.
The number of responsibilities will
continue to grow rapidly and
“go with the flow” will not
be the most effective strategy.
Our time management lectures will
provide new knowledge and skills
which will enable you to
:
· achieve desired results in less time
· establish priorities
· stop postponing
tasks until the last minute
· be able to focus on
a task and become more
conscious
· learn how to boost
your energy
· be familiar with best tools
for personal time management
and teamwork
We will also discuss
emotional intelligence,
how to develop it and how
it can improve the quality
of your relationships
with others.
The lectures will continue to discuss
relationships within a
working environment, providing
insight on teamwork:
- How to motivate and understand
team members
- What individual skills
are needed to build
responsible and productive
relationships at work
- How to make teamwork meet
your personal interests
and contribute to the
achievement
of shared goals
- How to become a valuable
member of a team
Last but not least, we will
discuss your ideas.
I am certain that in the course of
your scientific journey, you will
think of many progressive and
innovative ideas that can
change the world. But you will
need to know how to bring
them to life.
We will discuss
how to choose the right grant,
find sponsors and
promote your ideas to
a variety of audiences.
You might be surprised how
small these steps are,
but when correctly taken.
It can have an enormous
но верные шаги.effect on your results.
This Personal Effectiveness
module is dedicated to just that.
We would like to share these
life hacks with you.
See you, friends!